cardhunter.com 2017-12-15

# Card Hunter

## **BLUE MANCHU PRIVACY POLICY**

Effective **April 28, 2013**

This Privacy Policy serves to notify you of the following:

**Blue Manchu is a proprietary limited company with a principal place of business at 50 Holt St, Studio 103, Surry Hills, New South Wales, Australia (“Blue Manchu”/we/us/our)   maintains this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors/users of our Game and website(s), and when and how such information is collected, used, transferred, disclosed and safeguarded. This Policy also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their personal information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from Blue Manchu on an on-going basis.**

** ** **THE USE OF OUR SERVICES, GAMES, AND WEBSITE ARE SUBJECT TO AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY USING OUR SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED HEREIN WITH RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.   THIS PRIVACY POLICY ONLY ADDRESSES ACTIVITIES FROM OUR SERVERS. THIRD PARTY SITES (INCLUDING THOSE TO WHICH WE MAY LINK) AND THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS MAY HAVE THEIR OWN POLICIES, WHICH WE DO NOT CONTROL, AND THUS ARE NOT ADDRESSED OR CONTROLLED BY THIS POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OUR SERVICES OR ACCESS OUR SITES.**

Your privacy is important to Blue Manchu. To better protect your privacy, this policy is provided to explain Blue Manchu’s information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This privacy policy applies to user interactions that occur directly between Blue Manchu and both the commercial and non-commercial users of its services.  Such interactions often include intermediaries, such as restaurateurs and advertisers. _The privacy policy of intermediate parties may be different, and it is your responsibility to review these policies yourself._

### Information Collected

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted in relation to Blue Manchu services. When signing up for or utilizing services delivered by Blue Manchu, the following types of information may be collected:

  * Identification data (name, address, telephone, email address, etc.);
  * Electronic identification data (such as IP addresses, cookies, and log files);
  * Survey result and usage information;
  * Products or services ordered and delivered;
  * IM text and audio recordings;
  * Lists of your contacts;
  * Traffic data (data processed to convey or bill for communications, such as call duration and mobile number used to send SMS message);
  * Diagnostic information (data collected for purposes related to software or network operation, quality and maintenance, such as CPU, operating system, video card, sound card and memory information).
  * Billing and credit card information, if and when we begin to impose charges.

### **Consent to Monitor**

When you play Card Hunter, or use any of the communication features on the Card Hunter game or website, your IP address (the Internet protocol address from which you access any of the above) may be stored in our records. When the Card Hunter game is updated or “patched,” our patch routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of game-specific files; when you communicate on the Card Hunter website, within the Card Hunter game or any other communication feature on the Card Hunter website or within the Card Hunter game (e.g. live chat, instant message services and the like), even “privately” to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications that you send and receive.

### Blue Manchu’s Use of Your Information

In general, Blue Manchu uses the information it collects to provide services to you, to help us understand who uses the services, to improve the services, and to contact you for customer service and (if we commence charging) billing purposes.

We may use return email addresses to answer the email Blue Manchu receives or to deliver requested services to you.

We may use contact information provided via registration pages to provide technical support and periodically keep you informed of Blue Manchu news and product updates. You may opt-out of receiving this information at any time.

We may monitor and store user communications and, if we learn of improper or unlawful conduct, respond in accordance with this policy and our Terms of Service or Acceptable Use Policy.

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to provide you with customer support, to troubleshoot problems and to improve our products and services.

### Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or in our Terms of Service, or as specifically authorized by you, Blue Manchu will not disclose any information Blue Manchu gathers from you on the service.

**_Laws and Legal Rights._**

Blue Manchu may disclose your information (including personally identifiable information) if it believes in good faith that it is required to do so in order to comply with an applicable statute, regulation, rule or law, a subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process. Blue Manchu may also disclose personally identifiable information when it has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service for its services, or to protect the safety and/or security of itself, its users, or the general public.

**_Third Parties Generally._**

Blue Manchu may provide to third parties information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted, including where such information is combined with similar information of other users of the service. For example, Blue Manchu might inform third parties regarding the number of unique users who visit the service or the demographic breakdown of the registered users of the service. The third parties to which Blue Manchu may provide this information may include potential or actual advertisers, providers of advertising products or services (including vendors and website tracking services), commercial partners, sponsors, licensees, researchers and other similar parties.

**_Outside Contractors._**

Blue Manchu may employ independent contractors, vendors and suppliers (collectively, “Outside Contractors”) to provide specific services and products related to the Blue Manchu service, such as hosting and maintaining the service, providing credit card processing and fraud screening, and developing applications for the service. In the course of providing products or services to Blue Manchu, these Outside Contractors may sometimes have limited access to information collected on the service, including your personally identifiable information. We require that these contractors agree (1) to protect the privacy of your personally identifiable information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (2) not to use or disclose your personally identifiable information for any purpose other than providing Blue Manchu and its users with the products or services for which they are contracted.

**_Third Party Sellers._**

In addition, through the Blue Manchu service, you may be given the opportunity to purchase (or to obtain more information regarding) certain content, products or services that are sold by parties other than Blue Manchu (collectively, “Merchants”). We attempt to make it clear to you when you are dealing with a Merchant by opening a new browser or otherwise notifying you that you are leaving the Blue Manchu service. For example, if you see a phrase such as “powered by” or “brought to you by” followed by the name of a person or company other than Blue Manchu or the Blue Manchu service, then you are likely on, or about to enter, a Web site hosted or operated by a person or company other than Blue Manchu. Merchants may request that you submit certain information to them in order to purchase their products or services or to obtain additional information from them. By submitting the requested information, you affirmatively consent to have that information shared with the Merchant. This information is used by the Merchant and may be subject to a different privacy policy. _We are not responsible for the privacy practices of Merchants._ We encourage you to be aware when the Blue Manchu service links to Merchants’ web sites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every Merchant web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Blue Manchu service. We do not otherwise share or disclose your personally identifiable information to Merchants.

**_Sale of Business._**

Blue Manchu reserves the right to transfer information to a third party in the event of a sale, merger or other transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of Blue Manchu, provided that the third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**_Affiliates._**

Blue Manchu may disclose information (including personally identifiable information) about you to its Affiliates. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Affiliates” means any person or entity which directly or indirectly controls, is controlled by or is under common control with Blue Manchu, whether by ownership or otherwise. Any information relating to you that Blue Manchu provides to its Affiliates will be treated by those Affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Protection of Your Information

Blue Manchu strives to provide secure transmission of your information from your computer to Blue Manchu’s servers through industry-standard techniques.  For example, Blue Manchu has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures for the purpose of safeguarding and securing the information Blue Manchu collects from its users.

You should be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the Internet. There is also some risk that others could find a way to thwart security systems. As a result, while Blue Manchu strives to protect your information, Blue Manchu cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of any information you transmit to Blue Manchu, and you do so at your own risk.

### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy and online experience of children is especially important to Blue Manchu. For that reason, Blue Manchu never collects or maintains personally identifiable information from any person Blue Manchu actually knows is under 13 years of age. In addition, no part of the Blue Manchu service offering is designed for or directed to anyone under 13 years of age.

### **Accessing and Editing Your Information**

Corrections will not have an effect on other information that we maintain, or information that we have provided to third-parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy prior to such correction.

You may also opt-out from the continued use and processing by Blue Manchu of your personal data by sending Blue Manchu a request to support@bluemanchu.com. However, if you do so, Blue Manchu will not be in a position to provide its products and/or services to you.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to Blue Manchu from Blue Manchu’s system. The need to back up Blue Manchu’s systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your personally identifiable information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for Blue Manchu to locate. Therefore, while we can respond to your request for removal by making no further use of your personal data, except as stated in this Policy or required by law, it will often remain stored or archived in our system.

### **Data Retention**

Blue Manchu may retain your information for as long as it is necessary to: (1) fulfill any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or (2) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts. However, any information stored or archived in our system (as noted above) may be maintained until the applicable media are erased or destroyed.

### Modification to this Policy

Blue Manchu reserves the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Policy as it deems necessary at any time. We will inform you of these changes by directed notice (e.g., email to your known address) or by publishing the revised Privacy Policy online. The revised Privacy Policy shall become effective thirty (30) days after being so noticed or posted, unless you expressly indicate your acceptance of the revised notice earlier (for example by clicking on an “accept” button), in which case the revised Privacy Policy will become effective when accepted by you. You agree that the express acceptance by you, or your continued use of Blue Manchu software or services after the 30-day notice period, shall constitute your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the revised Privacy Policy, we will either cease all further use of your personal data or continue to use it in accordance with the policy previously in effect.

### **Third Party Sites**

As indicated above, the service may contain links to web sites not owned or operated by Blue Manchu (for example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement, you will likely be taken off the service). You should be aware that Blue Manchu is not responsible for the privacy practices of such web sites. Blue Manchu encourages you to be aware when the service links to other web sites and to read the privacy policies or statements of each and every web site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by the Blue Manchu’s service.

### **Contacting Blue Manchu**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send Blue Manchu an email at support@bluemanchu.com.

BY USING THE BLUE MANCHU SERVICE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE BLUE MANCHU’S SERVICE.
